<resources>

    <!--App-->
    <string name="app_name">Words</string>

    <!--List-->
    <string name="title_favorite">Favorite</string>
    <string name="title_recent">Recent</string>
    <string name="title_trending">Trending</string>
    <string name="list_banner_trending_body">Trending is a list of the most popular entries on Words, searched by other users.</string>
    <string name="list_banner_recents_body">Recents is where all your previous searches will appear.</string>
    <string name="list_banner_favorites_body">Favorites is where you can save words and come back to review important vocabulary.</string>

    <!--Search-->
    <string name="search_banner_body">Search results, recent searches and smart suggestions will all appear here.</string>

    <!--Notifications-->
    <string name="data_notification_channel_name">Data Notification</string>
    <string name="data_notification_channel_desc">Notifications which indicate the downloading, unpacking and preparation of dictionary data</string>
    <string name="data_seed_notification_title">Initializing Dictionary</string>
    <string name="data_seed_notification_text">Unpacking and loading words…</string>

    <!--Menus-->
    <string name="menu_favorite_title">Favorite</string>
    <string name="menu_share_title">Share</string>

    <!--Errors-->
    <string name="auth_error_message_unknown">An unknown error occurred during authentication</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_anon_login_unknown">Unable to log in anonymously</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_login_unknown">An unknown error occurred during log in</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_login_failed">Failed to log in</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_signup_unknown">An unknown error occurred during sign up</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_signup_failed">Failed to sign up</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_passwords_mismatch">Passwords don\'t match</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_no_current_user_to_link">No current user is available to create account with</string>

    <!--Auth Screen-->
    <string name="auth_email_hint">Email</string>
    <string name="auth_password_hint">Password</string>
    <string name="auth_confirm_passsword_hint">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="auth_log_in_button">Log in</string>
    <string name="auth_sign_up_button">Sign up</string>
    <string name="auth_cancel_button">Cancel</string>
    <string name="auth_error_message_empty_fields">Email and password must not be empty</string>

    <!--Settings Screen-->
    <string name="settings_night_mode_title">Night mode</string>
    <string name="settings_night_mode_desc">Reading late at night? Keep looking up words and give your eyes a break.</string>
    <string name="settings_about_title">About</string>
    <string name="settings_about_desc">Curious about where Words came from?</string>
    <string name="settings_contact_title">Contact</string>
    <string name="settings_contact_desc">Get in touch.</string>
    <string name="settings_email_compose_subject">Getting in touch</string>
    <string name="settings_email_compose_no_client_error">Looks like you don\'t have an email app installed</string>
    <string name="settings_header_create_account_body">Want to save your recent and favorite words? Want to continue to look up words with Merriam Webster definitions? Create an account and keep building your vocabulary or log in to restore your history.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_anonymous_free_trial_body">Want to save your recents and favorites across devices? Want continued access to Merriam-Webster definitions? Create an account to extend your Merriam-Webster trial and keep building your vocabulary or log in to restore your history.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_anonymous_none_body">Want to save your recents and favorites across devices? Want access to Merriam-Webster definitions? Create an account and keep building your vocabulary or log in to restore your history.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_anonymous_create_account_button">Create Account</string>
    <string name="settings_header_anonymous_log_in_button">Log in</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_none_body">Merriam-Webster is a plugin that inlines definitions, pronunciation, related words and examples right into Words entries. Help support Merriam-Webster and Words for an entire year of access.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_free_trial_expired_body">Looks like your free trial expired! Merriam-Webster is a plugin that inlines definitions, pronunciation, related words and examples right into Words entries. Help support Merriam-Webster and Words for an entire year of access.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_free_trial_body">You’re using a free trial of our Merriam-Webster plugin, an extension that inlines definitions, pronunciation, related words and examples into Words. Help support Merriam-Webster and Words with and get an entire year of access.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_subscribed_body">Merriam-Webster is a plugin that inlines definitions, pronunciation, related words and examples right into Words entries. You have unlimited access. Thank you for your support.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_subscribed_expired_body">Looks like your purchase expired! Merriam-Webster is a plugin that inlines definitions, pronunciation, related words and examples right into Words entries. Renew for a whole year of access.</string>
    <string name="settings_header_registered_add_button">Add</string>
    <string name="settings_sign_out_title">Sign out</string>
    <string name="settings_sign_out_default_desc">Sign out and log in with a different account.</string>
    <string name="settings_developer_title">Developer Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_developer_desc">Helpers to debug and alter configurations</string>

    <!--About-->
    <string name="about_header_body">
        Words is a dictionary concept designed to be an ergonomic, one-handable experience. In addition to being a great tool to improve your vocabulary, Words experiments with user experience and tries to solve modern problems on growing devices such as navigation, reachability and visual balance. \n\nThe idea for Words came when reading in bed, with a book in one hand and a phone in the other, trying to stretch a thumb to a far away search bar.
    </string>


    <!--Developer Settings-->
    <string name="developer_settings_clear_user_preferences_title">Clear user preferences</string>
    <string name="developer_settings_clear_user_preferences_desc">Reset user preferences to their default values</string>
    <string name="details_merriam_webster_card_details_button">Details</string>
    <string name="details_merriam_webster_card_dismiss_button">Dismiss</string>


</resources>
